		
		"DOTA_Tooltip_ability_abaddon_aphotic_shield_Description"				"Summons dark energies around the unit, creating a shield that absorbs a set amount of damage before expiring. When the shield is destroyed it will burst and deal damage equal to the amount it could absorb to an area around it. Removes certain types of negative buffs and stuns on cast.<br><br><font color='#70EA72'>Aphotic Shield can be used on enemies. Shield bursts immediately on enemies for max damage.</font>\n\nDISPEL TYPE: Strong Dispel"