		
		"DOTA_Tooltip_ability_arc_warden_flux_Description"						"Infuses a lone enemy unit with swirling, volatile energy, slowing its movement speed and dealing damage over time. The effect is muted if another enemy unit is near the target.<br><br><font color='#70EA72'>Flux can be used on allies or self.</font>"
		
		"DOTA_Tooltip_ability_arc_warden_spark_wraith_Description"				"Summons a Spark Wraith that slowly materializes and patrols a targeted area until an enemy comes within its range. Once a target has been found the wraith fuses with them, dealing magical damage and slowing the unit.<br><br><font color='#70EA72'>Spark Wraith affects allies too. Arc Warden changes the team briefly.</font>"
		