		
		"DOTA_Tooltip_ability_ancient_apparition_cold_feet_Description"			"Places a frozen hex on an enemy unit that deals damage over time, but can be dispelled by moving away from the initial cast point. If the enemy unit doesn't move outside of the given range, it will be stunned and frozen in place after 4 seconds.<br><br><font color='#70EA72'>Cold Feet can be used on allies or self.</font>"
		
		"DOTA_Tooltip_ability_ancient_apparition_ice_vortex_ff_Description"		"Creates a vortex of icy energy that slows movement speed and increases magic damage done in its range.<br><br><font color='#70EA72'>Ice Vortex affects allies too. Allies gain the positive buffs.</font>"
		
		"DOTA_Tooltip_ability_ancient_apparition_ice_blast_Description"			"Launches a tracer toward any location on the battlefield, which must be triggered again to mark the area to be blasted by a damaging explosion of hail. The further the tracer travels, the larger the explosion will be. Enemies caught in the explosion, or who touch the icy ball of hail as it travels, are Frostbitten, taking damage and prevented from regenerating or healing. If a Frostbitten unit's health drops below a certain percentage, they will instantly shatter.<br><br><font color='#70EA72'>Ice Blast can affect allies only if Ancient Apparition is within ~500 units of his allies upon launch. Ancient Apparition changes the team briefly.</font>\n\nUpgradable by Aghanim's Scepter."		
		